<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>新闻 on 爱酒人俱乐部</title>
    <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 新闻 on 爱酒人俱乐部</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh_cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://i9r.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>爱酒人俱乐部章程</title>
      <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/clubrules/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 17:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i9r.github.io/post/clubrules/</guid>
      <description>第一条 俱乐部性质
 爱酒人俱乐部是以葡萄酒酒爱好者个人为单元组成的一个民间社团，其对应的对象是品牌或机构。
 第二条 俱乐部宗旨
 &amp;ldquo;通过个人爱用者的社团，促进会员对红酒鉴赏的知识提高，最终形成一个红酒评价群众基础，团结个人单元，发出共同声音：打倒假酒！&amp;rdquo;
 共享——爱酒人俱乐部愿与机构和品牌共享信息化带来的便捷；共享知识、健康与快乐；共享与世界同步的信息文明。
 共创——爱酒人俱乐部愿与机构和品牌共创和谐平安的信息社会；共创商机、创新业务、创造价值；共同开创美好的未来。
 共进——爱酒人俱乐部愿与机构和品牌加强沟通交流、携手同心、共同进步。
 团购——爱酒人俱乐部愿与机构和品牌共同推动市场、加强团购力量，把液体黄金推荐给中国这个正在走向富强的20%的先富起来的那一部份中国人。
 第三条 会员服务
 爱酒人俱乐部以个性化服务的形式为会员提供更优质和优惠的产品与便捷的服务。
 以网站、期刊和活动的形式搭建爱酒人俱乐部与俱乐部会员之间的信息交流平台，使会员能够掌握业内最新信息。
 爱酒人俱乐部会不定期的为会员组织行业内专业品酒培训课程及业内名酒免费品鉴会。
 爱酒人俱乐部将邀请会员参加爱酒人俱乐部举办的定期/不定期的各种大型活动，以互动的方式促进会员企业之间的合作。
 第四条 会员活动的管理
 爱酒人俱乐部各项会员活动，均需确保俱乐部会员的利益。
 爱酒人俱乐部会及时通知和邀请会员参加俱乐部内外相关活动，并为会员提供完整的接待服务。
 第五条 入会
 爱酒人俱乐部实行会员制管理。使用爱酒人俱乐部业务的机构根据自愿的原则，在接受爱酒人俱乐部的邀请后，即可加入俱乐部，并由会员事务管理部为其办理相关手续。
 爱酒人俱乐部为所有正式会员提供年度会员卡，并提供相关的服务和利益。
 会员卡按年度进行更新，俱乐部管理委员会在每年年末向会员发放年度新卡。会员信息由职能部门负责定期收集和更新。
 第六条 会员权利
 加入爱酒人俱乐部的所有会员均自动成为爱酒人俱乐部的机构服务顾问，可随时向爱酒人俱乐部提出关于俱乐部服务方面的意见和建议。
 有关会员单位和会员单位代表的一切资料和信息，仅在爱酒人俱乐部内部使用，未经会员企业同意不会向任何其他方泄露。
 第七条 会员义务
 自觉遵守俱乐部的章程及活动规则。
 主动参加俱乐部所组织的活动。
 优先选择使用爱酒人俱乐部相关业务。
 及时提出使用爱酒人俱乐部各项业务的意见、建议和需求。
 不得故意损害爱酒人俱乐部和其他会员单位的企业形象以及俱乐部中其他会员的利益。
 需对俱乐部的内部事务及其活动进行相应的保密，尤其是不得在未经允许的情况下，泄露爱酒人俱乐部和其他会员单位的非公开性文件、资料等信息。
 在参加俱乐部组织的各项活动中，需遵从会员事务管理部的安排，同时，会员之间要彼此尊重、关心和帮助。如有异议，需本着友好协商、互相谅解的态度共同商讨。
 第八条 组织构架</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>富贵袋鼠在华进入快行道</title>
      <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/2018-01-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 17:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i9r.github.io/post/2018-01-31/</guid>
      <description>据相关数据显示，2017年10月，中国自澳大利亚进口瓶装葡萄酒6966万美元，同比增长75.8%。澳大利亚瓶装葡萄酒进口额首次超过法国（6376万美元），成为中国第一大进口葡萄酒来源地。
 对此国内进口商表示，按出口额计算，中国内地是目前澳大利亚葡萄酒第一大出口市场，其中澳大利亚葡萄酒的增速比其他葡萄酒出产国更快。在中国内地进口葡萄酒市场上，澳大利亚的市场份额占第二位，位于法国之后。但澳大利亚瓶装葡萄酒的平均价格，在中国进口葡萄酒市场的前五大国家当中位居第一。
 市场热度也带来了行业诟病，假酒、水货让澳洲葡萄酒在华经历一轮又一轮的信任危机。在国内进口商看来，假货泛滥是中国葡萄酒市场发展面临的巨大问题，这也反映出中国市场对葡萄酒的认知还处于入门级阶段，大多数人并不懂得如何辨别真假，才会使得商家存在侥幸心理。富贵袋鼠庄园作为为数不多直营中国市场的海外酒庄，以全产业链保障从澳洲葡萄园直供中国，从澳洲葡萄园-酿造-富贵袋鼠庄园中国仓库-富贵袋鼠庄园合作伙伴仓库-消费者，保证溯源。 富贵袋鼠葡萄酒精选南澳巴罗萨谷上好年份的最优质老藤葡萄，于1968年诞生了珍藏级RICH ROO富贵袋鼠葡萄酒，承载着人们对这片土地的记忆和辛勤忠实的劳作奉献。富贵袋鼠葡萄酒系列中的珍藏级富二代（R2）、富三代（R3），以及珍爱级的富六代（R6）、富七代（R7），在澳洲已经家喻户晓。 富贵袋鼠葡萄酒让世界一起分享这一珍贵的美味佳酿
2015阿德莱德国际葡萄酒挑战赛蓝金奖
2016阿德莱德质量大赛 - 金奖
2016、2017澳新银行杯- 金奖
2017年Wine100国际大赛银奖
2018年福建省婚庆行业协会春晚指定红葡萄酒
中国进口葡萄酒品牌G100最佳进口商   加盟热线 13806018052（微信同号）
   《爱酒人网》记者小蓉</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://i9r.github.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>